<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ChooseAdventureExample</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="ferris_bueller_smiling">Ferris Bueller Smiling</string>
    <string name="back_of_the_bus_story">You see your friend, Georgina, in the back of the bus. You
        go join her. A strange looking individual asks you if he can borrow a pen. You hand it to him
        while listening to Georgina\'s long story about the boy she likes. A few minutes pass and the bus
        stops at some train tracks. Suddenly, your eyes start watering, what is that horrible smell?
        The individual who borrowed your pen opens up the emergency exit at the back of the bus and
        jumps out, laughing along the way. The whole bus smells like rotten eggs. Apparently, he used
        your pen to open up a giant stink bomb on the bus. Finally the chaos settles and the bus is
        cleaned out and reboarded.

    </string>
    <string name="front_of_the_bus_story">You climb onto the bus and greet the bus driver. You notice
        a strange individual in the back whispering to your friend Georgina, you\'d like to talk to
        Georgina but something about that hoodlum doesn\'t seem right. Georgina clutches her bag tightly
        and moves away from the stranger, as does the other individuals sitting near him. You sit in
        the front row. The bus ride proceeds smoothly and arrives at the school.

    </string>
    <string name="chose_to_sit_in_back_title">Chose to Sit In Back</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="try_again">Try Again</string>
    <string name="play_again">Play Again</string>
    <string name="made_it_to_school">Made it to school</string>
    <string name="you_have_chosen_to_walk_to_school">You have chosen to walk to school. As you leave
        your house, you see your friends off in the distance. A car pulls up and blocks their view of you
        while they turn the corner. You contimplate whether you\'d get to school faster if you caught up
        with them, or if you walked alone. Which would be the better choice today?</string>
</resources>

